{
    "subject": "resource/Joyalukkas",
    "predicate": "property/homepage",
    "object": "http://www.joyalukkas.com",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of Joyalukkas is www.joyalukkas.com.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9813516736030579,
            "question": "Which website is the official homepage of Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9552153944969177,
            "question": "What is the website address for Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.940449059009552,
            "question": "What is the URL for the official website of Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9318000078201294,
            "question": "What is the web address used to access Joyalukkas's homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9267012476921082,
            "question": "How do you access the homepage of Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9080682992935181,
            "question": "To view Joyalukkas's homepage, what URL should you enter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9065288305282593,
            "question": "What is the web address for visiting Joyalukkas's main page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8986502289772034,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Joyalukkas online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8675711750984192,
            "question": "Where online can you find the primary information about Joyalukkas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8315030932426453,
            "question": "If you want to learn more about Joyalukkas, what website should you visit?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of Joyalukkas is www.joyalukkas.com.",
            "html": "dbpedia_870_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where online can you find the primary information about Joyalukkas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_870_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find information about Joyalukkas online?",
            "html": "dbpedia_870_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the web address for visiting Joyalukkas's main page?",
            "html": "dbpedia_870_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_870_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like me to analyze any more triples!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents contain information about the homepage URL of Joyalukkas being `www.joyalukkas.com`. Therefore, the statement cannot be confirmed based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no specific mention of the website address on any of the provided context information. The context only mentions visiting the Joyalukkas page on Almowafir, but not the main Joyalukkas website directly.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of text mention the website address as www.joyalukkas.in.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "I was informed through context information about the homepage of Joyalukkas which states \"About Joyalukkas Homepage\" but nowhere mentions that the homepage is www.joyalukkas.com. It only mentions that we are on Love Coupons website where we find all available Joyalukkas deals, this implies that the actual homepage is not mentioned in the provided context information and thus cannot be confirmed as www.joyalukkas.com",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context information mentions the website \"https://www.joyalukkas.in/pages/about-us\u2014joyalukkas-group/pgid-1248870.aspx\" for Joyalukkas, which is different from www.joyalukkas.com.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}